To celebrate your graduation among other things.
首先 祝贺你毕业
Roll your eyes at me again,
再对我翻白眼
and I will take you across my knee.
我就让你趴在我膝盖上
Oh.
噢
So it begins.
那就开始喽
Um.
嗯
Come on, I've something to show you.
来 给你看点东西
What?
啥呀
That's cute.
挺可爱的车呀
It doesn't really seem like your style though.
虽然和你风格不太像
That's not.
确实不像我的风格
Happy graduation, Anastasia.
毕业快乐   安娜斯塔西雅
Oh my god, Christian, that's a car.
额滴神啊   克里斯蒂安 那可是辆车呀
You don't miss much, do you?
你没损失多少 对吧
Thank you, but I can't. That... this is...
谢谢   但我不能 这也太
Do you like it?
你喜欢吗
Of course I like it, it's beautiful.
我当然喜欢它 它很漂亮
But I have a car. I have...
但是我有车呀 我有呀
Where is my car?
我的车哪去了
I told Taylor to fetch a decent price.
我让泰勒去把它卖了个好价钱
Oh, Christian, this is way too much.
哦 克里斯蒂安 这实在是太过分了
Did you just roll your eyes at me?
你刚才又对我翻白眼了